Finding Aid for Joyce Lindeman Papers 1950-1997
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Motion Pictures
  - Continuous Running Cartridges
    - Don Canham's Champions on Film
      - BioMechanics (Box 8)
      - Difficult Transitions (Box 8)
      - Force of Movement (Box 8)
      - Movements: Fast and Slow (Box 8)
      - Movements: Large and Small (Box 8)
      - Moving at Different Levels (Box 8)
      - Moving in Many Directions (Box 8)
      - Primary Propulsion (Box 8)
      - Propulsion Sculling (Box 8)
      - Simple Transitions (Box 8)
      - Stable Positions--Horizontal (Box 8)
      - Stable Positions--Vertical and Axial (Box 8)
      - Support Sculling (Box 8)
      - Training I (Box 8)
      - Training II (Box 8)
  - Super 8 Film
    - Houston, Texas
      - First and Second, Solo (Box 8)
      - First Place Team, Seniors (Box 8)
      - Second Place Team, Seniors (Box 8)
      - Third Place, Team (Box 8)
    - Gail Johnson and Theresa Anderson 1973 (Box 8)
    - Gail Johnson and Theresa Anderson; Amanda and Robin 1973 (Box 8)
    - Kathy Kretchmer and Amy Miner 1973 (Box 8)
    - Sara and Clara--A Team (Blank?) 1973 (Box 8)
    - Sheve Taylor and Jo Clare--San Antonio 1973 (Box 8)
    - Untitled (Box 8)
  - 8 mm Film
    - Senior Nationals
      - Florida, Solo Duet Team, Part I 1967 (Box 8)
      - Oklahoma, finals, Solo Duet Team 1968 (Box 8)
      - Ohio 1969 (Box 8)
  - Video Tape (open reel)
    - Michifish 1973, 2 tapes (Box 8)
    - Ruth Pickett, Figures for Degree of Difficulty Project April 28, 1981 (Box 8)
    - Unidentified (Box 8)
Additional material concerning the synchronized swimming team can also be found in the record groups for University of Michigan Athletics, University of Michigan Women's Athletics, and University of Michigan Women's Athletics Photographs which are also held by the Bentley Historical Library.